smartkiddies.com.au 2008-09-13

# Privacy policy of Smartkiddies maths

This policy covers the gathering of personal information by Smartkiddies and the way the information is handled by Smartkiddies PTY LTD.

At Smartkiddies PTY LTD we recognize the need to respect and protect any information gathered from the Smartkiddies website. We are committed to keeping safe and secure any personal information obtained from users. The information is transmitted and stored securely.

Why we collect information

  * To send confirmation of successful registration to members.
  * To provide access to restricted areas.
  * To give access to users to manage their own information.
  * To provide users with information.
  * To contact users regarding information about their accounts.

At Smartkiddies PTY LTD we will not give, rent or lease any personally identifying information about you to any individual, organization or company.

**Choice**

Users have a choice whether or not to provide information to Smartkiddies PTY LTD. However to gain access to restricted areas a users information is required. 

**Children**

As Smartkiddies is an Internet resource used by children we are well aware and committed to providing a safe and secure environment for children. For more information about protecting children online go to <http://www.netalert.gov.au/>

Smartkiddies PTY LTD does not collect personal information(name, age, address) directly from children. Parents/Teachers/Guardians provide Smartkiddies PTY LTD with information about their children upon registration to personalize usernames and passwords for each student using the site. Parents/Guardians have complete control over a child's membership that they have registered, at all times.

**Smartkiddies PTY LTD does not share with any 3rd parties information about a student's or school's results or progress.**

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file placed on a web browser. Smartkiddies uses cookies only for the purpose of managing user's membership and to enable services provided by Smartkiddies website.

**Securing usernames and passwords**

Ultimately users are responsible for the security of the usernames and passwords issued to them. It is recommended that usernames and passwords be kept safe and secure.

Smartkiddies PTY LTD is not responsible for any sites linking in or out of Smartkiddies website or any site referred to users by Smartkiddies. Smartkiddies PTY LTD recommends that users read the privacy policy of other websites before associating with it.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

Smartkiddies PTY LTD may change this policy from time to time. Therefore users are encouraged to check the policy periodically to read about any changes. Changes will be listed below. 

**Exemptions**

The only exemption to this privacy policy is if Smartkiddies PTY LTD were required by law or a court order to provide information. If you require more information about this policy please contact Smartkiddies.

Date Terms Issued, 21 Aug 2008 (GMT +10)
